Nine times out of 10, no problem.
- What happens on the 1 Oth time?
- Problem.
(Howard:)Hey, guys, before I forget,
l got you a little groomsmen present.
(Dimitri(in Russian):)- Thanks.
- You didn't have to.
Fantastic Four Annual Number 3
from 1965 in mint condition.
(Howard:)The one where Mr. Fantastic
and the lnvisible Girl get married.
(Leonard:)Oh, wow.
(Sheldon:)Oh, dear.
- l was afraid of this.
- What?
(Sheldon:)While a thoughtful gift,
this comic book in this condition...
- ...is worth at least $100.
- Yeah, so?
l bought you and Bernadette
a gravy boat worth $88.
(Sheldon:)Which places me in your debt,
and I can't be in your debt...
(Sheldon:)...because someday,
you might ask me to help you move...
(Sheldon:)...or to kill a man.
(Leonard:)I doubt he'll ask you to kill a man.
(Sheldon:)Well, what if it's his only way out?
I can't risk it.